<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PC on Iván Makes Games</title>
    <link>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/tags/pc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PC on Iván Makes Games</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 20:15:48 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ivodopiviz.github.io/tags/pc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Waiting for Horus</title>
      <link>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/waiting-for-horus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 20:15:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/waiting-for-horus/</guid>
      <description>Description: I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on updating this game to more modern technologies. Originally made with Unity 4.5 and RPC networking, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently migrating it to modern versions and reworking the netcode to use Steamworks P2P and server systems.
There&amp;rsquo;s still a lot of work to be done to adapt it to newer versions of Unity and to move it away of deprecated subsystems.
Technology: C#
Unity
Steamworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensar</title>
      <link>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/rehab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 20:35:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/rehab/</guid>
      <description>Sensar Description: This was a very interesting project for rehabilitation of patients with neuro-motor problems. It was a suite of minigames, all of them using the Kinect camera to detect gestures trained with machine learning techniques.
The main challenge was creating a system that would give accurate detection but at the same time allow to be configured lenient enough to account for each patient capabilities.
The system included user account support and full activity logging, intended to be shared with the medical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence</title>
      <link>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 18:53:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/silence/</guid>
      <description>Description: Small experimental sound-based game. The basic idea is to escape an alien ship using sounds as a guide. It was successfully greenlit but not yet released.
The most interesting part is the semi-procedural level generation system that takes partial Tiled maps and puts them together based on the desired difficulty of the level.
It&amp;rsquo;ll be eventually released for Windows, Mac and Linux.
Technology: Haxe
OpenFL
HaxeFlixel
Steamworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atmosphir</title>
      <link>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/atmosphir/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 20:16:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivodopiviz.github.io/portfolio/atmosphir/</guid>
      <description>Atmosphir Description: A very interesting project mix of platformer and level editor, made for the now defunct Minor Studios. The game was made with a very early version of what would eventually become Godot Engine and used Lua for scripting. Players could share their creations and challenge each map to set the fastest times.
This project would then move onto be developed by Minor Studios itself, getting ported to Unity and expanded significantly, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t involved anymore by that stage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>